Thank you.
Frameworks application framework is the core part of Android system.
It's mainly written in Java and C++.
You can find all the system services and core implementations of Android as of now.
Almost all the APIs are defined under Framework Base Core Java Android app called up or in Java Android
and then followed up.
And you can see that almost all the system services are defined under Framework Base Services Code Java
Quantum.
And these directories these services directories are typically more granular compared to APIs because
these can be refactored without the player API changes.
So as we discussed, you can find most of the apps and services under the Framework folder, so no framework
to base core Java Android.
So here you can find most of the API suites you use.
So these are the APIs which you use from the application.
The application developer basically refers to these packages while building the application.
And similarly, all the system services you can find under the services folder and here you have services
for Java Android and called for the intercom.
You can find common Android Salwar.
You can find almost all the system services.
For example, here you can see the activity manager and activity manager service class.
You can find here see this one.
And similarly, the package manager should be here to BBM.
So this one does this package manager?
Well, there should be a package manager service.
That's this one.
And similarly, you can find almost all the services, all the system services here.
This is the power manager or manager service.
So under Frameworks folder, these are the two major folders which you need to be aware about.
There are many other folders where we have many other services and APIs, but these two folders are
the core folders.
I can't.